export const termsAndConditions = [
  {
    topic: "Introduction",
    questions: [
      {
        question: "Our Terms & Conditions",
        answer:
          "Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet consectetur adipisicing elit. Deserunt in quos blanditiis natus dolore iusto aut veritatis iste rerum eveniet?",
      },
      {
        question: "Collection of personal data",
        answer:
          "Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet consectetur, adipisicing elit. Fuga mollitia non fugit, amet laborum natus?",
      },
      {
        question: "Purpose of collection of personal data",
        answer:
          "Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet consectetur, adipisicing elit. Fuga mollitia non fugit, amet laborum natus?",
      },
      {
        question: "Usage of your personal data",
        answer:
          "Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet consectetur adipisicing elit. Deserunt in quos blanditiis natus dolore iusto aut veritatis iste rerum eveniet?",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    topic: "Payment Terms",
    questions: [
      {
        question: "Different payment methods on our website",
        answer:
          "Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet consectetur adipisicing elit. Deserunt in quos blanditiis natus dolore iusto aut veritatis iste rerum eveniet?",
      },
      {
        question: "Our right to cancel your payment",
        answer:
          "Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet consectetur, adipisicing elit. Fuga mollitia non fugit, amet laborum natus?",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    topic: "Orders",
    questions: [
      {
        question: "Order processing on our website",
        answer:
          "Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet consectetur adipisicing elit. Deserunt in quos blanditiis natus dolore iusto aut veritatis iste rerum eveniet?",
      },
      {
        question: "Dispatch and shipping times for different types of orders",
        answer:
          "Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet consectetur, adipisicing elit. Fuga mollitia non fugit, amet laborum natus?",
      },
      {
        question: "Return and refund policies for all online orders",
        answer:
          "Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet consectetur, adipisicing elit. Fuga mollitia non fugit, amet laborum natus?",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    topic: "Changes",
    questions: [
      {
        question: "Our right to change Terms & Conditions",
        answer:
          "Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet consectetur adipisicing elit. Deserunt in quos blanditiis natus dolore iusto aut veritatis iste rerum eveniet?",
      },
      {
        question: "Notice of change in Terms & Conditions",
        answer:
          "Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet consectetur, adipisicing elit. Fuga mollitia non fugit, amet laborum natus?",
      },
    ],
  },
];
